<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="en-US">
    <voice name="en-US-AvaNeural">
        Good afternoon.
        My name is Henry.
        Thank you very much for this opportunity for an in-depth discussion.
        I am a software engineer with over 10 years of experience, and Java backend development has been the central thread throughout my technical career.
        I've always been passionate about leveraging technology to build robust, efficient systems and solve practical business challenges.
        For me, writing code is more than just completing tasks; it's about creating value and overcoming complex problems.
        For instance, in a recent project I was involved in, the 'Object Standardization Platform,' our core challenge was abstracting diverse business objects into a unified, extensible structure while providing high-performance data services.
        I was deeply involved in designing its core model, implementing the microservices architecture based on Spring Cloud, and utilizing Redis for performance optimization.
        This platform ultimately provided effective support for multiple product lines within the company.
        In a previous 'PDM SaaS' project, working as a System Engineer, I had the opportunity to apply Domain-Driven Design to handle complex manufacturing business logic.
        I also explored the design and implementation of multi-tenant architectures.
        This experience significantly honed my ability to tackle complex system design and challenges within distributed environments.
        These experiences solidified my understanding that excellent technical solutions must not only be functionally complete but also possess strong maintainability, scalability, and robustness.
        My years in the industry have exposed me to various sectors, including banking, manufacturing, and human resources, and I've held diverse roles ranging from development to management.
        This has allowed me to build a comprehensive tech stack – I'm proficient in the Java ecosystem, familiar with the full Spring suite, MyBatis, databases, testing frameworks, and more.
        It has also cultivated my ability to analyze problems from multiple perspectives: technical, business, and managerial.
        I am very familiar with Agile development methodologies, Git-based collaboration workflows, and Docker containerization technology.
        Regarding the English proficiency requirement for this role, I am comfortable reading technical documentation and requirements without difficulty and can communicate effectively in writing.
        As for AWS S3 and RDS, I understand their importance in cloud-native architectures.
        Based on my understanding of general cloud service patterns and my strong ability to learn quickly, I am confident I can rapidly master and apply these technologies.
        What attracts me to this Senior Java Engineer position is the opportunity it presents to refocus on solving challenging technical problems in a dedicated environment.
        Your company's advocated engineering culture, remote collaboration model, and emphasis on technical depth align strongly with my expectations.
        I am confident that my experience, passion for problem-solving, and my work style – which emphasizes proactive communication and taking ownership – will allow me to integrate well into the team and make valuable contributions.
        I look forward to the possibility of discussing in more detail how my experience can bring value to your team.
        Thank you!
    </voice>
</speak>
